JULIEN AFONSO

WEB DEVELOPER

KYOTO - JAPAN



- **1** 090-8880-4393
- ju.afonso61@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/julienafonso/
- https://github.com/JulianTheOne
- https://julienafonso.me/

SKILLS

- HTML5
- Figma
- CSS
- Git/GitHub
- Bootstrap
- Heroku
- JavaScript
- Ruby
- SQL
- Ruby on Rails

LANGUAGE

- French (Native)
- English (Full professional proficiency)
- Japanese (Professional working proficiency)

EDUCATION

LE WAGON TOKYO | BATCH #1105

Web Development certification (2023)

10-week intensive Full stack Developer bootcamp.

AFT-IFTIM CERELOG

Bachelor degree (2009)

Logistics, Materials and Supply Chain Management.

PROFILE

Curious by nature, I moved to Japan 9 years ago and I have experience in Supply Chain, Sales, and E-commerce. I have transitioned into tech after learning coding. I love using logic to solve problems and I am eager to work in a collaborative, multi-cultural team environment.

EXPERIENCE

SALES ASSISTANT

Mercedes-Benz Kyoto Chuo (Jan 2022 - Dec 2022)

- Vehicule inspection continuation / Desired number application /
 Owner name change application / Registration / Parking certification
- New car/Used car delivery preparation / ETC set-up

CO-FOUNDER

The Omamori Shop (Jul 2020 - Dec 2022)

- Shopify E-commerce connected to Ship&co API to optimize worldwide shipping (from 5 min to 20 sec per order).
- Ads manager for multi-platform campaigns
- Collaboration with famous Japanese car Shop & US based influencers
- 3800+ orders and \$170.000+ in sales

TRAVEL SALES CONSULTANT

Au fil du Japon - Freelance (Jul 2017 - Apr 2020) Autrement le Japon (Sep 2014 - Oct 2016)

- Travel agent specialized on tailor made trip for B2B and B2C
- Accompanying travelers & VIP (Kyoto Osaka)
- 700+ pax / ¥281,000,000+ in sales

WAREHOUSE MANAGER

BASF Coatings Services S.A. (Apr 2010 - Mar 2014)

- Logistics, inventory management with audit (KPMG), cost control, tester for ERP updates before national release (SAP)
- From 2.5M stock value to 1.3M by optimizing stock rotation